Educational Technology Services Records UA245
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Great Courses, 2014 -- 2017; UA245.001; 626 Digital Object(s); 1 Web sites
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 2., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.377
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 3., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.378
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 4., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.379
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 5., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.380
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 6., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.381
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 7., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.382
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 8., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.383
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 9., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.384
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 10., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.385
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 11., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.386
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 12., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.387
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 13., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.388
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 13 - 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 1 -- Overview of the Course;Ptolemaic Astronomy -- Part 14., 2014-09-02; gc.phil167.389
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 1, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Complete., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.390
    Section: Class 2, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 1., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.391
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 2 - Part 3., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.392
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 2 - 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 4 - Part 5., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.393
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 4 - 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 6., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.394
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 7 - Part 8., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.395
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 7 - 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 9., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.396
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 10 - Part 11., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.397
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 10 - 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 12., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.398
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 13., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.399
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 14., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.400
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 2 -- 16th Century Astronomy: Copernicus and Tycho Brahe -- Part 15., 2014-09-09; gc.phil167.401
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 2, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Complete., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.402
    Section: Class 3, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 1 - Part 2., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.403
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 1 - 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 3., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.404
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 4., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.405
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 5., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.406
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 6., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.407
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 7., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.408
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 8., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.409
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 9., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.410
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 10., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.411
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 11., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.412
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 12., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.413
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 13., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.414
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 3 -- Kepler's Astronomia Nova: The Orbit of Mars -- Part 14., 2014-09-16; gc.phil167.415
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 3, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Complete., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.416
    Section: Class 4, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 1 - Part 2., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.417
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 1 - 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 3., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.418
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 4., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.419
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 5., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.420
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 6., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.421
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 7., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.422
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 9., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.424
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 10., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.425
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 11., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.426
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 12 - Part 13., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.427
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 12 - 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 14., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.428
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 15., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.429
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 16., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.430
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 16.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 4 -- Kepler's Planetary System and the Rudolphine Tables -- Part 17., 2014-09-23; gc.phil167.431
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 4, Part 17.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Complete., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.432
    Section: Class 5, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 1., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.433
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 2., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.434
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 3., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.435
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 4., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.436
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 5., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.437
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 6., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.438
    ViGenerally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 7., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.439
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 8., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.440
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 9., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.441
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 10., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.442
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 11., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.443
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 12., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.444
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 13., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.445
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 14., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.446
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 5 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1609 to 1642 -- Part 15., 2014-09-30; gc.phil167.447
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 5, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Complete., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.448
    Section: Class 6, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 1., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.449
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 2., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.450
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 3., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.451
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 4., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.452
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 5., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.453
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 6., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.454
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 7., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.455
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 8., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.456
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 9., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.457
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 10., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.458
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 11., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.459
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 12., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.460
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 13., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.461
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 14., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.462
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 15., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.463
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 6 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Local Natural Motion -- Part 16., 2014-10-7; gc.phil167.464
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 6, Part 16.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Complete., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.465
    Section: Class 7, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 1., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.466
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 2., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.467
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 3., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.468
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 4., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.469
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 5., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.470
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 6., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.471
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 7., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.472
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 8., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.473
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 9., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.474
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 10., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.475
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 11., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.476
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 7 -- Galileo's Two New Sciences: Projectile Motion -- Part 12., 2014-10-14; gc.phil167.477
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 7, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Complete., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.478
    Section: Class 8, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 1., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.479
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 2., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.480
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 3., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.481
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 4., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.482
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 5., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.483
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 6., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.484
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 7., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.485
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 8., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.486
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 9., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.487
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 10., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.488
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 11., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.489
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 12., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.490
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 13., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.491
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 8 -- Descartes' Principia: Laws of Motion -- Part 14., 2014-10-21; gc.phil167.492
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 8, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Complete., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.493
    Section: Class 9, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 1., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.494
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 2., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.495
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 3., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.496
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 4., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.497
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 5., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.498
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 6., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.499
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 7., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.500
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 8., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.501
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 8.